Well, today is the music video shooting for AL4EA!
I'm at school now.
I heard it's a real school.
It's a weekday.
I wonder if there might be some students there.
Haruma.
This is a real school, not just an abandoned school.
I heard it's a real school.
It's a weekday!
Weekday!
I wonder if there are people here.
Maybe they're studying downstairs.
We'll be up there shooting music videos.
Let's see what's going on today.
Good morning.
It's like YouTube.
Surprise! I ate my whole lunch!
I can see it right here.
Bacon and eggs and
Aloedo
Aloe drink
Aloe drink sandwich
Aloe Drink Sandwich
It's colorful!
What's aloe?
You're a Moroccan!
Wait, where's Alo?
Where's the food?
I'm trying to open it.
It's like you can't open it.
Ah! It's open!
What's this?
Cole slaw salad and
Tomato
Tomato & Turkey.
Bon appétit!
Oh, you'll be mischievous when you get there.
There you go.
Tea eyes
Hello! I'm in a tall building in Yoyogi, Tokyo.
Today, we are shooting a music video for Yale For You.
So, the cast members are here, so let me introduce them to you!
This is Mr. Eech!
Yay!
Yes, we are going to shoot the music video now. We will do our best!
Thank you!
I like to dance while watching here!
It's so emo!
It's great!
Keep it up, but get some rest!
Both of you, together.
Sasaki-san, watch out.
So, I will do my best in this cold weather.
Let's do our best.
I'll say it again and again, hang in there.
Hang in there.
Don't worry, me.
I will do my best.
It's cold.
I'll do my best.
Let's go one more time. Please roll the camera.
♪ To the one I want to meet ♪
♪ I can't stop, I love you more I love you more
I love you more I love you more
Don't worry, no matter what words I choose, they'll never reach you.
Good morning.
Oh, no, it's already done.
Here it is.
I'll warm you up.
I'm gonna warm you up.
There you go.
You got it.
Thank you very much.
It's cold and dry.
Yes, it is.
It's cold
It's true
You
It's cold
how did you like it?
Hello vastu in sweetness
strawberry
I'm here
Snack
I made a real swing and a miss
I made a mistake.
It's so cold I don't know how to swing.
You're smiling so much.
You're having so much fun, what are you talking about?
I'm having so much fun.
Yay!
Older and younger.
Of course they are.
Yay.
How are you today?
Today.
Cold.
It's cold.
We like it cold.
It's really cold.
Seriously.
I was just on the 21st floor.
There's no fence on the roof.
I'm scared.
I was peeking in like this.
I was saying to myself, "Wow!
It's really scary.
I just want people to see it.
It's like...
Bye bye.
Stay tuned for the next video.
- You know what I mean?
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- This one.
- Yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah!
- By the way, the hair is so poofy.
- Here.
- Oh!
- Oh, I'm so sorry.
It's windy, windy, windy, but my bangs aren't moving.
But it doesn't look like it's moving at all.
Thank you very much.
I'll do my best.
I'll do my best. Even in the cold.
It's not cold. I'm getting small fry.
Here we are on the 21st floor.
21st floor. Too fickle, too chewy.
Go girls.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
Go, go, go, go, go. Clap your hands here.
How's it going?
This is the way to go.
If we're in love together
Last, last, last
The last.
If I miss you and realize I love you
I'll get over any worries
I'll say it again and again Don't worry
I love you with I to I
I'm sure you'll be fineI'm sure you'll be fine
Wish upon a blue sky
Air for you
It'll come true
A cheer for your love
Thank you
Cut!
Applause
Thank you!
We'll have another dance on the rooftop once we're done.
That's all, if you don't mind.
Thank you very much!